thegateacademy.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Statement | THE GATE ACADEMY

You are here: [Home](http://thegateacademy.com/) / Privacy Statement

This Privacy Policy describes the information, as part of the normal operation of our services, we collect from you and what may happen to that information.  
Please read this privacy policy to learn more about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information. By accepting the Privacy Policy and Service Agreement in registration or by visiting and using the Site, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the THE GATE ACADEMY Service Agreement

**A Special Note About Children**

Persons under the age of 13 are not eligible to use the Site. If you are 13 year old and above but under the age of 18, you may use this Site and submit personal information to us only in conjunction with and under the supervision of your parents or guardians.

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information when you register on our site or fill out a form.  
At different places you may be asked to provide your information like name, e-mail id, address, choices, preferences etc. You may also visit our site anonymously but for certain services we require this information.

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

Some of our Web pages utilize “cookies” and other tracking technologies. A “cookie” is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Web site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser.

Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Web site and your Web experience. We may also analyze information that does not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics.

**What do we use this information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

>   * To personalize you experience
>   * To maintain your feedback to improve our website(your feedback help us to better respond to your individual needs).
>   * To help you in your Exam preparation. We maintain your information to record your test history, your discussion history etc.
>   * To help you track your college applications and reduce efforts
>   * To send periodic emails
> 

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?  **

We do not sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conduct our business, or servicing you, as long as those third parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

THE GATE ACADEMY corporated law enforcement enquiries. Therefore, in response to a verified request by law enforcement or other government officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, city, province, telephone number, email address, UserID history.

**Control of Your Password**

You are responsible for all actions take with your User ID and password. Therefore, we do not recommend that you disclose your Www.thegateacademy.com password to any third parties. If you choose to share your User ID and password or your personal information with third parties, you are responsible for all actions taken with your account and therefore you should review that third party’s privacy policy before doing so. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password by going to your account page.
